Contact

lonestarjen@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jennifer-trombley-rn (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

RN

Certified Medical Surgical RN Leadership

Jennifer Trombley, BSN, RN

School Nurse AISD at Dell Children's Medical Center Foundation Austin, Texas Area

Summary

Registered Nurse with over 11 years of experience in ED, Med/ Surg, Psychiatry and School Nursing. 6 years of management and supervisory experience in the hospital setting. Disaster Relief Volunteer with the American Red Cross. Graduate of the Wilderness Medicine Institute (NOLS): EMT-B, Wilderness First Responder

Experience

Dell Children's Medical Center Foundation School Nurse AISD July 2019 - Present (1 year) Austin, Texas

Baylor Scott & White Health RN, Psychiatry August 2018 - Present (1 year 11 months) Austin, Texas Area

HCA Healthcare RN, Nurse Manager- Medical/Surgical November 2010 - Present (9 years 8 months)

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington BSN, Nursing

Sterling College

Associate of Arts - AA, Resource Management · (1996 - 1998)

NOLS

Wilderness Medicine Institute, EMT and Wilderness First Responder